[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Bob Gale originally wrote Back to the Future, the time machine was which of the following?", "correct_answer": "Refrigerator", "incorrect_answers": ["Phone booth", "Wrist watch", "Delorean"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which 2002 movie was based on the life of real life musician Wladyslaw Szpilman (played by Adrian Brody)?", "correct_answer": "The Pianist", "incorrect_answers": ["The Italian Job", "In America", "Gosford Park"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the Big Bad Wolf wearing all the time in the 2001 animated comedy movie Shrek?", "correct_answer": "A pink nightgown", "incorrect_answers": ["A white bridal gown", "A tuxedo", "A sheep skin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Iron makes up 35.1 % of Earth. 28.2 % is oxygen. What is the third leading element of Earths composition?", "correct_answer": "silicon", "incorrect_answers": ["magnesium", "nickel", "calcium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous rock musician directed Born to Boogie a 1972 movie about English rock band T. Rex?", "correct_answer": "Ringo Starr", "incorrect_answers": ["Elton John", "Mickey Finn", "Marc Bolan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If HCl and NaOH are combined, what compound is produced other than water?", "correct_answer": "NaCl", "incorrect_answers": ["HNa", "HOH", "ClOH"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This medical term refers to a decrease in the number of circulating leukocytes (white blood cells) in the blood.", "correct_answer": "Leukopenia", "incorrect_answers": ["Lymphoma", "Leukemia", "Leukocytosis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What percentage of humans have type O blood?", "correct_answer": "45 %", "incorrect_answers": ["33 %", "25%", "There is no way to tell."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Love has given me wings so I must fly. (2001)", "correct_answer": "A Knights Tale", "incorrect_answers": ["Phenomenon", "Ever After", "Forget Paris"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the chemical symbol for Uranium?", "correct_answer": "U", "incorrect_answers": ["Ua", "Ur", "Un"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who invented the ball point pen?", "correct_answer": "Jozsef Laszlo Biro", "incorrect_answers": ["Elias Schaeffer", "Elias Howe", "John Fitzsimmons Waterman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sir Isaac Newton developed his calculus and physics at what college?", "correct_answer": "None", "incorrect_answers": ["Oxford", "Trinity", "Cambridge"]}]